

Profile

An Aspiring Junior Front-end Developer with 2 years+ of experience developing production-ready application with React.js/Next.js with Typescript, MUI5, tailwind ,React-Native and more in frontend side. Furthermore, experienced mongodb, firebase, node.js and express.js for backend side as well.

Employment History

Software Developer, HKU SPACE

MAY 2024

- Developed and maintained HKU SPACE ERP systems with React.js.
- Digitized internal paper work system to e-form with Microsoft Power-App and Power-automate.

Front-end Developer, Protek Intelligence Asia

FEBRUARY 2022 - APRIL 2024

- Created and maintained web applications for Governmental Project of Warehouse Management System with Next.js/Typescript, MUI 5, Node.js and mongodb.
- Created and maintained web applications for Warehouse Management System/
 Warehouse Execution System of DFS group with React/Typescript and Sass.
- Created widget Dashboard with Elastic search and Kibana to show several widgets for displaying status of tracking items.

Front-End Developer Intern, ST ENGINEERING (Hong Kong) Ltd

JUNE 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- Worked as Software Development Intern to support 4GMS Project(Fourth Generation Mobilizing System) in Hong Kong Fire Services Department with React.js.
- In charged of software development using React.js, node.js and MYSQL to embody the location finding function.

IT Trainee, LEXIWAVE Technology (Hong Kong) Ltd,

JANUARY 2020 - MAY 2020

- Industrial Pre-Training Program from City University of Hong Kong.
- Used Python to receive data from a MIMO Radar module and applied Yolov3, Retina-net, and the CNN Machine Learning Algorithm to implement object recognition with the received data.

IT Trainee, Siemens Digital Industries Software Korea

JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2019

- Web UI/UX Design participation.
- Helped team to build a modern and responsive theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout with CSS.

Education

 $Computer\ Data\ Engineering\ Bachelor\ Degree, City\ University\ of\ Hong\ Kong$

SEPTEMBER 2014 - NOVEMBER 2021

Details

Kowloon

Hong Kong

+85294828013

hohunsjoo11177@gmail.com

Links

Portfolio

LinkedIn

Github

Skills

HTML 5

CSS3

JavaScript

Typescript

React.js

Next.js

Tailwind CSS

SASS

MUI 5

Redux/Redux ToolKit

React-Query

React-Native

Native-Base

Microsoft Power-App

Microsoft Power-Automate

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

Keycloak

Git

PHP

Laravel

Languages

Korean

English

Mandarin